Go to the GitHub Astrid repository:
https://github.com/astrid-project/astrid-framework
Download the code
Move into the installation script folder
Install the Astrid Framework
(Context Broker and Astrid Controller)
Checking Context Broker installation
(Lens IDE for Kubernetes https://k8slens.dev/)
Checking Astrid Controller installation
Installation and configuration of Astrid Framework is completed
Proceed with installation of two types of Execution Environments
Installation and configuration of a single Execution Environment with Filebeat activated
The Execution Environment installation is completed
Installation and configuration of two Execution Environment with Polycube activated
To install the Astrid Dashboard link to https://github.com/astrid-project/security-dashboard/blob/master/cut.mp4