Go to the GitHub ASTRID repository:
https://github.com/ASTRID-project/ASTRID-framework
Download the code
Move into the installation script folder
Install the ASTRID Framework
Checking Context Broker installation
Lens IDE for Kubernetes - https://k8slens.dev
Checking ASTRID Controller installation
Installation and configuration of ASTRID Framework is completed
Proceed with installation of 2 Execution Environments
Installation and configuration of Execution Environment n. 1 with Filebeat activated
Installation of Execution Environment n. 1 is completed
Installation and configuration of Execution Environment n. 2 with Polycube activated
Installation of Execution Environment n. 2 is completed
To change the agent configurations and see the status of each component
install the ASTRID Security Dashboard (https://github.com/ASTRID-project/security-dashboard)
Video: https://github.com/ASTRID-project/security-dashboard/blob/master/cut.mp4